Hi, welcome to the program.
嗨 欢迎来到本课程
We're thrilled to have you here and I'm looking forward to guiding
你能来到这 我们都很兴奋 我很期待充当你的向导
your journey through the cutting edge of artificial intelligence.
带你游览人工智能的发展前沿
You are now an essential member of the Udacity community.
现在你已经是优达学城社区不可或缺的一份子了
We're here to make sure you fulfill your goals,
我们优达学城既要帮你完成目标
but we also want to learn from you.
也想向你学习
Your experience will guide future development and we would love to hear
你在这的经历将引领我们未来的发展方向 我们欢迎
your thoughts on how we can improve and make this program better for others.
你谈谈自己的感受 告诉我们要如何改善这个课程 以便他人从中获益
Now, let's take a quick walk through
现在 我们先迅速参观一下
the Udacity office to get a flavor of how we do things here.
优达学城的办公室 看看我们在这都做些什么
So we believe in learning by doing.
我们认为要通过实践来学习
So rather than simply watching videos or taking tests on AI,
所以你不仅要看视频、做有关人工智能 (AI) 的练习
you'll build real artificial intelligence and watch those AIs,
你还得动手创建真正的人工智能 观察这些 AI
solve complex problems that humans like me and
解决复杂问题的过程 而这些问题若是让你我等人类来解决
you simply can't do with the same speed or accuracy.
是没有办法解决得那么快或那么准确的
In the first project, you build
在第一个项目里 你要创建
a simple AI agent that solves any Sudoku problem in the world.
一个简单的人工智能体 让它帮你解任意数独问题
And learn two foundational AI techniques;
同时 你会学到人工智能的两个基本技术
constraint propagation and search.
约束传播和搜索
This project is just a little teaser to get your feet wet and show you how
这个项目只是个小测试 让你热热身 让你了解
quickly you can start applying AI concepts to problems around you. Hey Kristina?
要应用 AI 的概念来解决身边的问题 是不用等很久的 嗨 Kristina?
Hey Dhruv.
嗨 Dhruv
You will also been given the chance to go
你还有机会使用高级数独技巧
above and beyond by using advanced Sudoku strategies,
提高智能体的处理速度
to improve the speed of your agent.
做得比我们更好
In the next project, you'll build any AI agent
下一个项目 你要创建的智能体
that can routinely defeat opponents in isolation.
总是能在孤立游戏中打败对手
Here you apply minimax and alpha-beta pruning.
在这个项目里 你要使用极大极小值算法和 alpha-beta 剪枝算法
Two strategies used by Google world beating Go agent, AlphaGo.
谷歌那个世界一流的 Go agent 也即 AlphaGo 用的就是这两个算法
You go on to create an AI that guides Pac-Man through his maze and
接着 你要创建一个人工智能 让它来指引吃豆人走出迷宫
allows him to eat all the food in the most efficient way possible.
同时还要让他以最高效率吃掉所有食物
Definitely more efficient than Ryan over here.
绝对要比这边的 Ryan 高效
I'm still practicing.
我还在练习呢
Using simple techniques such as;
使用简单的技术 如
breadth-first search, depth-first search and A-Star Search.
宽度优先搜索、深度优先搜索和 A* 搜索算法
Your AI agent will traverse Pac-Man Maze faster than any human player.
就能让你的智能体比任何人类玩家走出吃豆人迷宫的速度都要快
Next, you'll be tasked with finding the optimal route
再接着 你的任务是找出最优路径
for taking cargo from one place to another.
来将一处的货物运送到另一处
Planning problems like this,
这种规划问题
are the very core of the logistics industry.
是物流业的核心
And you'll see just how powerful AI is in solving these kind of problems.
届时你会发现 人工智能在处理这类问题时有多强大
And finally, you use hidden Markov models to automatically read
最后 你要用隐马尔可夫模型来自动识别
sign language characters and convert them into their English text counterparts.
手语字符并将其转化为相应的英文文本
This is just one of the many examples of how
这只是一个应用而已
AI is making a meaningful impact in society at large.
人工智能还有许许多多其它应用 足见其正深刻地影响着整个社会
And, all this is just in timeline.
我说的这些项目会按时间表来开展
We think you'll have a lot of fun and we can't wait to see you get started.
相信你会学得很开心 我们都迫不及待地和你启程了